[Music]
Hello friends, welcome to our YouTube
channel Marine World. Friends, in today's
video, I will
tell you in great detail about Airtel Life Insurance.
Friends, before continuing in the video,
I would like to request you that if
you haven't subscribed to this channel yet, then
please subscribe to it
and if you like this video, then
please share it. So friends, let's
start the video with this. Friends,
Indian Airtel has
introduced two recharge plans for its prepaid customers,
which also provide the benefit of life insurance to the customers on recharging their prepaid
number.
Friends,
first of all, Indian Airtel has launched a
term life insurance plan of Rs 400,000 in collaboration with HDFC Life for Rs 279 in 2019.
Friends, if you recharge for Rs 299, then
you will be provided a term life insurance policy of Rs 4 lakh for
free.
Friends, after this,
another recharge pack of Rs 189 has been launched by Indian Airtel.
In this recharge plan, Indian
Airtel has collaborated with Bhartiya Ekta Life.  The
benefit of term life insurance of 2 lakhs has been
provided to its customers. Friends,
if you recharge for Rs 1 to 79 i.e. 179, then
you will be
given term life insurance of 2 lakhs for free.
Friends, at present, Indian Airtel is
providing the benefit of life insurance on its two recharges.
I am telling you in detail about these two recharge plans.
Friends, on Airtel's
prepaid recharge of Rs 219 i.e. 279,
you get 28 days validity and
in this you get unlimited national calls free
and in this you
get 1.5 GB data free every day and you
get 100 SMS free every day. Friends,
in this plan you get term life insurance of ₹400000 from HDFC Life.
Friends, if we talk about Airtel's
prepaid recharge of Rs 1 to 79 i.e. 179, then in this
you get 28 days validity and
in this you get unlimited national calls free for
28 days.  And in this you get full 2GB
data and you get 300 SMS
friends, in this plan
you get free term life insurance of ₹2 lakh from Bharti Airtel XLife.
Friends, as soon as
you recharge your number with any of these two recharge packs,
you will
get a policy action message on your number. Friends, this life insurance policy
customer care registered number will be issued.
After this, the customer can
fill in their address and their details on their Airtel Thanks Up or they
can go to any Airtel retailer near them and fill in their details. Friends,
talking about the eligibility for Airtel Life Insurance, for Airtel Life Insurance, the
customer's minimum age for Airtel Life Insurance is 18 years and
maximum age is 54 years. Friends,
Airtel Life Insurance policy will be made only
in the name of the registered SIM card holder
and the name cannot be disclosed later.
Friends, no medical test is required for this policy.
Friends, no action is required for this policy.
To get a physical copy of the policy, you need to provide your address.  You can
update your policy through Airtel Thanks Up or by
visiting your nearest retailer. Only then can a
physical copy of the policy be sent to your home.
Friends, customers can update the nominee through Airtel Thanks Up.
Friends, let's talk about how Airtel Life Insurance works.
When an Airtel prepaid
customer recharges their mobile number with one of the Indo plans,
a policy
action message is sent to their mobile number. This policy is
issued to the customer care registered number.
Friends, after this, the customer is given the option to enter
their home address and other details by going to their Airtel Thanks Up.
Customers
can also get this done through any of their Airtel retailers.
Friends, the
death benefit is paid to the person nominated by the individual through Airtel Life Insurance.
Therefore, it is
advised that as soon as you
recharge with this recharge plan, you should
carefully fill in the nominee's details
so that the benefit can easily be passed on to the nominee in case of your death.  It
should also be kept in mind that this policy is
issued only in the name of the registered SIM card holder. There is
no provision for changing the name in this, hence
it is important that you carefully check your registered name.
Friends, let's talk about
how to apply for Airtel Life Insurance policy. So friends, to
get Airtel Life Insurance policy,
you have to follow some steps.
Friends, first of all, you have to recharge your Airtel number
with Airtel recharge of Rs. 179 or 279, 189 or 289.
As soon as you
recharge your Airtel number with any of these recharges, the
policy is automatically issued
and an action message is
sent to your registered Airtel mobile number.
Friends, now you have to
go to your Airtel Thanks Up and update your home address and important details.
Friends, you can get these details
filled through your nearest retailer only.
After this, a
physical copy of your Airtel Insurance policy will be sent to your home.
So friends, in today's video,
we learned what Airtel Life Insurance is
and in detail about it, I told you guys.  I have
explained it in detail in today's video. If
you liked this video, then do
share it with your friends and if you are
new to the channel, then do subscribe to it.
See you in the next video
with some other topic. Till then, thank you
[Music]